<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Classinfo</string>
    <string-array name="Title">
        <item> Timetable </item>
        <item> Subjects </item>
        <item> Faculty </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Description">
        <item>Say bye to fussy image timetable</item>
        <item>Brief syllabus of every subject</item>
        <item>Get your faculty info here</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Week">
        <item> Monday </item>
        <item> Tuesday </item>
        <item> Wednesday </item>
        <item> Thursday </item>
        <item> Friday </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Monday">
        <item>Signals and Systems</item>
        <item>Mathematics</item>
        <item>Networks and Protocols</item>
        <item>Digital Circuits and Systems</item>
        <item>Devices and Networks Lab</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time1">
        <item>9.30AM - 10.20AM </item>
        <item>10.30AM - 11.20AM </item>
        <item>11.30AM - 12.20PM </item>
        <item>12.30PM - 1.20PM </item>
        <item>3.00PM - 5.50PM </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Tuesday">
        <item>Network Analysis and Synthesis</item>
        <item>Signals and Systems</item>
        <item>Mathematics</item>
        <item>Networks and Protocols</item>
        <item>Electrodynamics and EM Waves</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time2">
        <item>9.30AM - 10.20AM </item>
        <item>10.30AM - 11.20AM </item>
        <item>11.30AM - 12.20PM </item>
        <item>12.30PM - 1.20PM </item>
        <item>3.00PM - 3.50PM </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Wednesday">
        <item>Electrodynamics and EM Waves</item>
        <item>Network Analysis and Synthesis</item>
        <item>Signals and Systems</item>
        <item>Mathematics</item>
        <item>Digital Circuits and Systems</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time3">
        <item>9.30AM - 10.20AM </item>
        <item>10.30AM - 11.20AM </item>
        <item>11.30AM - 12.20PM </item>
        <item>12.30PM - 1.20PM </item>
        <item>3.00PM - 3.50PM </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="Thursday">
        <item>Electrodynamics and EM Waves</item>
        <item>Network Analysis and Synthesis</item>
        <item>Signals and Systems</item>
        <item>Digital Electronics Lab</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time4">
        <item>10.30AM - 11.20AM </item>
        <item>11.30AM - 12.20PM </item>
        <item>12.30PM - 1.20PM </item>
        <item>3.00PM - 5.50PM </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Friday">
        <item>Networks and Protocols</item>
        <item>Digital Circuits and Systems</item>
        <item>Electrodynamics and EM Waves</item>
        <item>Network Analysis and Synthesis</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time5">
        <item>9.30AM - 10.20AM </item>
        <item>10.30AM - 11.20AM </item>
        <item>11.30AM - 12.20PM </item>
        <item>12.30PM - 1.20PM </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Subjects">
        <item>Mathematics</item>
        <item>Signals and Systems</item>
        <item>Network Analysis and Synthesis</item>
        <item>Electrodynamics and EM Waves</item>
        <item>Digital Circuits and Systems</item>
        <item>Networks and Protocols</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Mathematics">
        <item>Real Analysis: Real number system. Sets, relations and functions. Properties of real numbers.Sequences. Cauchy sequences. Bolzano-Weierstrass and Heine-Borel properties.</item>
        <item>Reimann integral. Mean value theorems. Sequences and series of functions. Pointwise and uniform convergence. Power series and Taylor series.</item>
        <item>Probability Theory: Random Variable and random vectors - Distributions and densities. – Functions of one and two random variables. Moments and characteristic functions</item>
        <item>Random processes - Strict sense and wide sense stationary processes - Covariance functions and their properties - Spectral representation - Wiener-Khinchine theorem.</item>
        <item>Gaussian processes – Poisson processes - Lowpass and Bandpass noise representations.</item>
        <item>1. W.Rudin, “Introduction to Principles of Mathematical Analysis”, McGraw-Hill International Editions, Third Edition, 1976.
            \n2. Davenport,” Probability and Random Processes for Scientist and Engineers”, McGraw-Hill, 1970.
            \n3. Papoulis. A.,” Probability, Random variables and Stochastic Processes”, McGraw Hill, 2002.</item>
        <item>1. Kreyszig.E. “Advanced Engineering Mathematics”, John Wiley, 1999.
            \n2. S.C. Malik, Savita Arora, “Mathematical Analysis”, New Age International Ltd, 4th Edition, 2012.
            \n3. G.B.Gustafson and C.H. Wilcox, “Advanced Engineering Mathematics”, Springer Verlag, 1998.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Signals_and_Systems">
        <item>Definition of Signals and Systems, Classification of Signals, Operations on signals, Singularity functions and related functions. Analogy between vectors and signals - orthogonal signal space, complete set of orthogonal functions, Parseval’s relations. Fourier series representation of continuous time periodic signals -Trigonometric and Exponential Fourier series- Properties of Fourier series.</item>
        <item>Fourier transform of aperiodic signals, standard signals and periodic signals - Properties of Fourier transforms. Hilbert transform and its properties. Laplace transforms-RoC-properties. Inverse Laplace transform.</item>
        <item>Continuous-time Systems and its properties. Linear time invariant (LTI) system-Impulse response. Convolution. Analysis of LTI System using Laplace and Fourier transforms.</item>
        <item>Sampling and reconstruction of band limited signals. Low pass and band pass sampling theorems. Aliasing. Anti-aliasing filter. Practical Sampling-aperture effect.</item>
        <item>Discrete-time signals and systems. Discrete Fourier series. Z-transform and its properties. Analysis of LSI systems using Z – transform.</item>
        <item>1. A.V.Oppenheim, A. Willsky, S. Hamid Nawab, “Signals and Systems (2/e)”, Pearson 200.
              \n2. S.Haykin and B.VanVeen “Signals and Systems, Wiley, 1998.</item>
        <item>1. M.Mandal and A.Asif, “Continuous and Discrete Time Signals and Systems, Cambridge, 2007.
             \n2. D.C.Lay, “Linear Algebra and its Applications (2/e)”, Pearson, 200.
             \n3. S.S.Soliman and M.D.Srinath, “Continuous and Discrete Signals and Systems”, Prentice- Hall, 1990.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Network_Analysis_and_Synthesis">
        <item>Network concept. Elements and sources. Kirchhoff’s laws. Tellegen’s theorem. Network equilibrium equations. Node and Mesh method. Source superposition. Thevenin’s and Norton’s theorems. Network graphs.</item>
        <item>First and second order networks. State equations. Transient response. Network functions. Determination of the natural frequencies and mode vectors from network functions.</item>
        <item>Sinusoidal steady-state analysis. Maximum power-transfer theorem. Resonance. Equivalent and dual networks. Design of equalizers.</item>
        <item>Two-port network parameters. Interconnection of two port networks. Barlett’s bisection theorem. Image and Iterative parameters. Design of attenuators.</item>
        <item>Two-terminal network synthesis. Properties of Hurwitz polynomial and Positive real function. Synthesis of LC, RC and RL Networks, Foster Forms and Cauer Forms.</item>
        <item>1. Hayt W. H., Kemmerly J. E. and Durbin S. M., “Engineering Circuit Analysis”, 6th Ed., TataMcGraw-Hill Publishing Company Ltd., 2008.
              \n2. F.F. Kuo, “Network analysis and Synthesis”, Wiley International Edition, 2008.</item>
        <item>1. Valkenberg V., “Network Analysis”, 3rd Ed., Prentice Hall International Edition, 2007.
              \n2. B.S.Nair and S.R.Deepa, “Network analysis and Synthesis”, Elsevier, 2012.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Electrodynamics_and_EM_Waves">
        <item>Electrostatics. Coulomb’s law. Gauss’s law and applications. Electric potential. Poisson’s and Laplace equations. Method of images. Multipole Expansion.</item>
        <item>Electrostatic fields in matter. Dielectrics and electric polarization. Capacitors with dielectric substrates. Linear dielectrics. Force and energy in dielectric systems.</item>
        <item>Magneto-statics. Magnetic fields of steady currents. Biot-Savart’s and Ampere’s laws. Magnetic vector potential. Magnetic properties of matter.</item>
        <item>Electrodynamics. Flux rule for motional emf. Faraday’s law. Self and mutual inductances. Maxwell’s Equations. Electromagnetic Boundary conditions. Poynting theorem.</item>
        <item>Electromagnetic wave propagation. Uniform plane waves. Wave polarization. Waves in matter. Reflection and transmission at boundaries. Propagation in an ionized medium.</item>
        <item>1. D.J.Griffiths, “Introduction to Electrodynamics (3/e)”, PHI, 2001
             \n2. E.C. Jordan and G. Balmain, “Electromagnetic Waves and Radiating Systems”, PHI, 1995.</item>
        <item>1. W.H.Hayt, “Engineering Electromagnetics, (7/e)”, McGraw Hill, 2006.
              \n2. D.K.Cheng, “Field and Wave Electromagnetics, (2/e)”, Addison Wesley, 1999.
              \n3. M.N.O.Sadiku, ”Principles of Electromagnetics, (4/e)”, Oxford University Press, 2011.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Digital_Circuits_and_Systems">
        <item>Review of number systems-representation-conversions, error detection and error correction. Review of Boolean algebra- theorems, sum of product and product of sum simplification, canonical forms-min term and max term, Simplification of Boolean expressions-Karnaugh map, completely and incompletely specified functions, Implementation of Boolean expressions using universal gates.</item>
        <item>Combinational logic circuits- adders, subtractors, BCD adder, ripple carry look ahead adders, parity generator, decoders, encoders, multiplexers, de-multiplexers, Realization of Boolean expressions- using decoders-using multiplexers. Memories – ROM- organization, expansion. PROMs. Types of RAMs – Basic structure, organization, Static and dynamic RAMs, PLDs, PLAs.</item>
        <item>Sequential circuits – latches, flip flops, edge triggering, asynchronous inputs. Shift registers, Universal shift register, applications. Binary counters – Synchronous and asynchronous up/down counters, mod-N counter, Counters for random sequence.</item>
        <item>Synchronous circuit analysis and design: structure and operation, analysis-transition equations, state tables and state diagrams, Modelling- Moore machine and Mealy machine- serial binary adder, sequence recogniser, state table reduction, state assignment. Hazard; Overview and comparison of logic families.</item>
        <item>Introduction to Verilog HDL, Structural, Dataflow and behavioural modelling of combinational and sequential logic circuits.</item>
        <item>1. Wakerly J F, “Digital Design: Principles and Practices, Prentice-Hall”, 2nd Ed., 2002.
            \n2. D. D. Givone, “Digital Principles and Design”, Tata Mc-Graw Hill, New Delhi, 2003.</item>
        <item>1. T. L. Floyd and Jain,”Digital Fundamentals”, 8th ed., Pearson Education, 2003.
            \n2. S.Brown and Z.Vranesic, “Fundamentals of Digital Logic with Verilog Design”, Tata Mc-Graw Hill, 2008.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Networks_and_Protocols">
        <item>Network Components, Topologies, Network hardware and software, Network Models: OSI Model and TCP/IP Protocol stack, HTTP FTP, SMTP, POP, SNMP, DNS, Socket programming with TCP and UDP.</item>
        <item>Transport Layer services, UDP, TCP, SCTP, Principles of reliable data transfer, Flow control, Congestion Control, Quality of Service.</item>
        <item>Network Layer services, Datagram and Virtual circuit service, DHCP, IPV4, IPV6, ICMP, Unicast routing protocols: DV, LS and Path vector routing, Multicast routing.</item>
        <item>Data Link Layer services, Overview of Circuit and Packet switches, ARP, Data link control: HDLC and PPP, Multiple access protocols, Wireless LAN, Comparison wired and wireless LAN.</item>
        <item>Network security threats, Cryptography, Security in the Internet: IP Security and Firewalls, Multimedia: Streaming stored video/ audio, RTP, Network Troubleshooting.</item>
        <item>1. J.F.Kurose and K.W.Ross, “Computer Networking: A Top-Down Approach featuring the Internet”, Pearson, 5th edition, 2010.
            \n2. B.A. Forouzan,” Data Communications and Networking”, Tata McGraw- Hill, 4th edition, 2006</item>
        <item>1. W.Stallings, “Data and Computer Communications”, PHI, 9th edition, 2011.
            \n2. W.Stallings, “Cryptography and Network Security”, Pearson, 5th edition, 2011.
            \n3. A.S.Tanenbaum and D.J. Wetherall, “Computer Networks”, Pearson, 5th edition, 2014.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>Unit 1</item>
        <item>Unit 2</item>
        <item>Unit 3</item>
        <item>Unit 4</item>
        <item>Unit 5</item>
        <item>Text Books</item>
        <item>Reference Books</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Faculty_name">
        <item>Dr.Abhijit Das</item>
        <item>Dr.P.Palanisamy</item>
        <item>Dr.Ashish Patil</item>
        <item>Dr.P.Muthuchidambaranathan</item>
        <item>Dr.G.Lakshmi Narayanan</item>
        <item>Dr.B.Rebekka</item>
        <item>Dr.G.Thavasi Raja</item>
        <item>Ms.R.K.Kavitha</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Dr.AbhijitDas">
        <item>8093329659</item>
        <item>abhijit@nitt.edu</item>
        <item>Mathematics</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Dr.P.Palanisamy">
        <item>9486001111</item>
        <item>palan@nitt.edu</item>
        <item>Signals and Systems</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Dr.AshishPatil">
        <item>8147185954</item>
        <item>abhijit@nitt.edu</item>
        <item>Network Analysis and Synthesis</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Dr.P.Muthuchidambaranathan">
        <item>8148264183</item>
        <item>muthuc@nitt.edu</item>
        <item>Electrodynamics and EM Waves</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Dr.G.LakshmiNarayanan">
        <item>9442940144</item>
        <item>laksh@nitt.edu</item>
        <item>Digital Circuits and Systems</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Dr.B.Rebekka">
        <item>8148264193</item>
        <item>rebekka@nitt.edu</item>
        <item>Networks and Protocols</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Dr.G.ThavasiRaja">
        <item>9443485798</item>
        <item>thavasi@nitt.edu, g.thavasiraja@gmail.com</item>
        <item>Digital Electronics Lab</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Ms.R.K.Kavitha">
        <item>8148264132</item>
        <item>rkkavitha@nitt.edu</item>
        <item>Devices and Networks Lab</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>